{
    "subject": "resource/Death_at_a_Funeral_(2010_film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Regina_Hall",
    "human_readable": "Regina Hall stars in the 2010 film 'Death at a Funeral'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8425442576408386,
            "question": "What film did Regina Hall star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709678411483765,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.637165904045105,
            "question": "What other films has Regina Hall appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5869178771972656,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'Death at a Funeral' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822360515594482,
            "question": "Is Regina Hall known for comedic roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776544809341431,
            "question": "Name an actor who appeared in the film 'Death at a Funeral'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46497291326522827,
            "question": "Would you recommend the film 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42328473925590515,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Death at a Funeral' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4147617518901825,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a plot point from the movie 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3605037331581116,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or remakes of 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Regina Hall stars in the 2010 film 'Death at a Funeral'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2947_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a plot point from the movie 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2947_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Death at a Funeral' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2947_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you recommend the film 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2947_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2947_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Regina Hall is mentioned as an actress who starred in multiple films (Girls Trip, etc.), she is not mentioned specifically as starring in the 2010 film 'Death at a Funeral'. However, her co-star Peter Dinklage is mentioned in relation to both the original UK production of \"Death at a Funeral\" and the US remake."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Regina Hall's role in the 2010 film \"Death at a Funeral,\" which confirms that she starred in this movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Regina Hall actually stars in the 2017 film \"Girls Trip\", not in the 2010 film \"Death at a Funeral\".",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}